Uploaded by [ sRtFeVeR ] new srt source
Ah, lust. What is it about
these physical pleasures? So
licentious, so lascivious, that
they've led so many to ruin.
[Music]
After all, wasn't it lust in her
eyes that lead Eve to take a
bite out of that Apple. Or the
Greeks to war with Troy. Yes,
even the strongest, the bravest,
the most brutal can be undone by
lust. For centuries, kings,
queens, Popes and presidents
have all given in to their most
primal instincts. Caligula had
his orgies, Cardinals had their
concubines and even highborn
rulers like Catherine the
Great's sexual appetites were
so enormous, legend has it she
could ultimately only be
satisfied by a horse. Yes,
they say lust knows no mercy but
for one man it
also knows no age.
[Music]
>> Childhood was great. There
was nothing really out of the
ordinary. Great family.
Over the years I've
dated various looks
here and there. Some men they
like blondes. Some men like
brunettes. Some men like fat
women. Some men like men. I knew
like early on that girls my age
aren't really my thing.
I want to say that I was
in 6th grade and there was a
teacher who would always
sit in front of the class
and she would sit on the
stool wearing skirts and she
would cross her legs back and
forth. She was hot, I knew
instantly. She was probably 68,
69 years old. I remember the
first thing I ever searched on
the Internet, ever. I mean, I
knew early on. One of the
questions I've been asked, o.k.,
Kyle, let's say I put a Sports
Illustrated swimsuit model in
front of you next to an older
woman, which one are you going
to go for? I would look at the
Sports Illustrated girl and I
would think, okay, looking at
her, she was pretty. I bet her
grandma is gorgeous. Everyone
is wired. You don't have a
choice. You like what you like
because your brain is hardwired
that way. Aging is a part of
life and it is natural
and I like that look. I like
wrinkles. I like the neck line.
I like gray hair. Yeah, I like
boobs. A little, even a hell of
a lot of saggage, it's fine, I
mean it's normal. It's going to
happen. To me, dentures are
like the unicorn of oral sex.
It's something that you look
for. It's like trying to find
that four leaf clover. That's
the one, it's awesome. So, here
I am in high school. You know, I
was trying to get a date with
an older woman. They weren't
having it. They were like you
are so young. No one told me
how to do it. I had to go out
there with trial and error.
But I got better at it. I mean,
I realized you know, how to talk
to a woman. It doesn't hurt to
know who Tony Bennett is.
I found that places like grocery
stores is a good place to go up
and complement someone and say,
hi. You know what, take a
chance. Just take a chance. Have
one date and see what happens.
>> I met Kyle on a dating site.
I told him you should find
someone your own age. And I
told him this a couple of times.
I think it was the 3rd time
he said, well just have dinner
with me. So, I agreed to have
dinner with him. And we met for
dinner and I instantly liked
him. I was very nervous because
I knew I hadn't had sex for a
while. So we were undressed and
I even got more afraid because
I thought, I don't think that's
going to fit. So. But he
made me feel very comfortable.
Never once did he seem awkward
to be with me. We would be out
in public and he would hold my
hand and kissed me. That feels
just great that someone his age
could like someone my age.
>> Me and Anna, our sex life
it's awesome. Sometimes, like
she'll just grab me by my
throat which is really cool
because she looks so
innocent and so unassuming.
>> I think if you stop having
sex because of your age or
you've lost your spouse or
whatever, I think that you're
really missing out
on a part of life.
>> No one wakes up one day and
goes, well you know what guys,
today I'm 73 and it's time to
stop having sex and it's time to
start being boring and shit.
No one ever does that.
>> I live in a senior complex.
The average woman there, all
they want is their time alone.
They are not interested in sex
or men, period.
I got into doing gang
bangs in 2008. I've done 14
since and each one is
better than the last one.
Yeah, it's like if you taste a
new ice cream and you like it,
you don't just have it once.
[Laughter]
>> Shirley is a lot
like me in the sense of,
neither one of us are
looking for that relationship.
>> The first time Kyle and I
had sex, we just enjoyed each
other's bodies. He's a
wonderful lover, he's a giver.
>> We have hard, rough sex.
There is hair pull and there's
body and there's scratching.
>> Do you want specifics?
>> [Off-screen] Oh, yeah.
>> Some people out there might
not even know what squirting is
but Kyle can make me squirt
over and over and over.
>> I don't hold back, I don't
go easy. I mean, older women can
take it. They can have
sex just like anyone else can.
>> I don't think Kyle was easy
on me as far as sex because I am
older than he is.
I am 91 years old.
I would date a man my own
age, but there aren't any.
Of the people who graduated with
me, there are only 2 of us
living. I think sex was a big
part of life. It must have been,
I have 6 kids. When Kyle first
came over, he brought a dozen
rubbers and 3 boxes of Astro
glide. I said, what do you think
you're going to do with that
Astro glide, I make my
own lubrication. Right.
[Laughter]
>> And then he grabbed me and
kissed me. It was earth
shattering, believe me. I have
not been kissed like that for a
long time.
Do I still have orgasms?
Yes, I do.
Shouldn't I?
>> I do enjoy, I guess capturing
the moment. I tried to take
pictures of the women that I
date and I like to shoot videos
as well. And those videos, they
stay on my hard drive. They are
just for me to have. Older
women, they are just like other
women. You know, all women enjoy
attention and affection. They
like being told they're pretty
or attractive. They like to feel
desired. The only
difference is they are older.
>> I am just sorry that I didn't
start it sooner. A lot of the
years of my life, I could
have had a lot more fun
and enjoyed myself.
>> Yeah, if you only knew
you would be happy, too.
>> I mean, I think at my age you
get to the point where you don't
give a hoot what people think.
>> They haven't kept you living.
I've kept myself. Does that
sound wrong? Does that sound
selfish or anything? I don't
know. I just lived so long. You
can't imagine. Anybody who's
younger can't imagine what it's
like. It's just like, probably
maybe what people do when
they do dope. It gives you
a big shot. It's the best.
>> Who are you to put
limitations or to put asterisks
next to your mom or your grand
mom's happiness. If you
can't be happy that they are
happy then you are a bad person.
Period.
[Music]
>> Lust, how it makes us do
so many, many wicked things.
What if the true answer to
controlling our most unbridled
passions is just
giving into them.
>> I probably became an
ordained minister because it
was my mother's intention that I
enter the ministry. I attended
divinity school starting
in the fall of 1952.
I was a respected lobbyist in
the wedding chapel game.
I said that I would
represent brothels.
Women are not the
same creature once they
are married and settled down as
when they were on the prowl and
they were looking for a husband.
Once they get the little
cottage or the white picket
fence, the 2-year-old twins and
the puppies to take care of, the
gentleman and his sexual needs
kind of pushed to the back
burner. And I think the man who
discreetly goes to a brothel
can save a marriage.
Brothels, they are
saving marriages.
[Music]
>> George, hi, George.
>> Baby, hi how are you. Kylie,
come sit down here.
>> Hi, how are you.
>> It's good to see you my lady.
>> It's good to see you too.
This is Alexis.
>> Hello, Alexis. My pleasure.
>> Nice to meet you.
>>Come in Christie. I always get
quizzed because I am a minister,
and my position is this.
In biblical history,
Jesus' best friend was Mary
Magdalene. She was a
prostitute. So Jesus is
confronted in the streets of
Jerusalem by this group of men
who are ready to stone this lady
and they said that she was
caught in sin, she was nothing
but a simple, plain, prostitute.
And he looked down at her, and
he said, let him and who is
without sin cast the 1st stone.
And everybody put their stones
on the ground and walked off.
And then Jesus said to Mary, now
Mary go thy way and sin no more.
What did he really mean by that?
Did he mean, don't continue
your profession? Or did he mean,
don't take it to heart that it's
wrong. The Bible does not tell
us that she quit being or that
she stopped being a prostitute.
[Music]
>> The type of women that work
in brothels are a unique amalgam
>> When a client
walks in the door,
the hostess calls the lineup.
She will say, the ladies are
going to introduce themselves.
>> Hi, I'm Barbie.
>> Hi, I'm Hollywood.
>> Hi, I am Melissa Kiss.
>> Hi, I am a Eva Grace.
>> Hi, I am Christie Kiss.
>> Hi, I am Carmen Sage.
>> I am Alyssa Fox.
>> When the men enter and
they see all of us lined up,
they seem nervous.
>> Because, I just don't like
picking someone out of a crowd.
>> I feel guilty, because
I don't want to pick any
one person out and
make the others feel bad.
>> Then, she will ask him to
select a girl of his choice.
>> As a woman, it can be very,
very nerve-racking, as well.
Just because, you know,
you want to get picked.
>> You know what, there
are some kids that come in,
very young kids.
And we're just like, oh no
the babies are in and we
generally get picked by the
younger, the younger guys.
They are just gaga, with the
big guys. Oh my gosh,
I just want a cougar so bad.
[Laughter]
>> Were going to need 1300 cash.
Okay.
[Sexy Music]
>> If men weren't very
sexually inclined,
pretty soon we
would all die off.
>> I'll do pretty much what ever
they like to do. At like an
anal party or something
like that, I don't like
the real quickies.
>> He wanted me to pretend like
I was cooking a lobster in this
bathtub in this sauna and
calling my friends on the phone
and inviting them
to this big dinner.
>> Golden showers, Roman
showers, and brown showers.
I get a lot of
golden shower requests.
>> There is a lot of guys
who come in with a fetish.
Maybe their wife doesn't feel
comfortable doing, or maybe they
don't even feel
comfortable talking about.
>> You may have that fear, I
have to see this person every
day and they are going to
know that I like butt plugs.
[Laughter]
>> Where is the average man
supposed to go for a sexual
release if he weighs 375 pounds?
Where is the average man
supposed to go for a sexual
accommodation if he has lost
both arms in the Vietnam War?
>> If somebody is willing to be
open with me, I am willing to
work with them. If they're shy,
or they don't know how to go
down on their wife. Or, you
know, they just need to get this
tension and frustration out.
They just need a release.
>> The longer you're married,
the less oral sex seems to be a
paramount thing for a wife.
Men need blow jobs
to put it bluntly.
>> I would tell you this, if I
was going to get remarried, I
would've probably married and an
ex-working girl. Because they
are smart in so many ways
as far as taking care of
and pleasing a man.
>> Why have you made
this your cause?
>> I believe in it. It minimizes
so many of the negatives
that exist everywhere else.
Some people golf,
I protect this industry.
[Music]
>> Many men do not come to a
brothel for the select purpose
of having sexual intercourse.
Many of these men come for the
company and the touch. There is
nothing more important to a man
then the touch of a female.
>> It could be going out to a
restaurant or something like
that. Or it could just be
cuddling in bed and sharing
secrets and talking
about feelings.
>> A lot of times men just come
in here and just want to talk.
>> A lot of these men actually
really love their wives.
They still have an emotional
connection with them but the
physical connection just
may not be there anymore.
>> Their wives had surgeries,
older women hysterectomies,
cancer, chemotherapy and they
just can't have sex. For the
most part the married men, they
love their wives. They would
never think of doing anything
like this outside of here.
They come here because,
because they're safe and
it's not cheating.
>> Well, you know, I have a
special one in here that I've
been seeing and I have known her
for about, going on four years,
I guess.
>> Look at you, how are you?
>> Should we get 3 girls
tonight? That'll be fun or Go
out, we could go shooting.
We could go to Virginia city.
>> I'm retired so I like to goof
around and it's something to do.
>> They are coming in for some
type of fulfillment and I am
here for that. Communication,
companionship, a snuggle or just
a night of wild sex.
>> Come on in.
>> Why should I feel guilty?
>> He was very naughty boy
and then he went home and was
probably a really
good boy to his wife.
>> We are married
and happily married.
>> We have a 2-year-old son.
I was a stay-at-home mom.
>> I am married and I have
children. 4 of them, actually.
And they have children,
9 of them actually.
>> I mean, I wish more people
could be like us. Where we can
tell each other the deepest
darkest secrets and know that
he's going to keep them safe.
>> At the end of the day,
I know that she loves me.
And at the end
of the day, I know that we are
in a committed relationship.
>> Keep your love for each
other, always an unselfish love.
Keep this between your love of
complete and total devotion,
a love in the faith in all
things and through all
situations will carefully
and devotedly always try.
Always think of
the other person first.
We see every day, regardless
of your professional choice;
minister, politician, architect.
The chances are that you are
going to have your own times
where your morals are tested
and tried. It's very
shortsighted for anybody to
condemn a minister who does
certain things that may not be
typically traditional in
society. And I think I can say
even as Jesus did, let him that
is without sin cast the first
stone. If Jesus were around
today, he'd probably say George,
just keep up the good work.
>> How we do live in a world of
such endless possibilities.
Just take a look at the folks
over at Exotic Erotics. They are
currently putting a different
spin on the beast with 2 backs
[Music]
>> I feel that horses are the
most beautiful animals. Oh, the
way they move, the way their
muscles work. I'm not sure
exactly where my fascination
with a horses came from.
I don't know,
I can relate to them.
I am the owner of Exotic
Erotics. We are the only
company that makes
adult sex toys that are
cast from live animal genitalia.
[Music]
>> Life casting is the process
of making a copy of a living
object. Our specialty is making
life casts of animal genitalia
to be turned into adult toys.
I live in a very rural area.
Horses play a really big role.
Honestly, I have no idea what
most people would do if they
knew what I did for a living.
Well, first before we start
casting, we have to make sure
all our materials are set up so
that we are ready to go on a
moments notice because the whole
casting process takes less than
10 minutes. We have to have a
stallion. Someone brings in a
mare that is in heat and she
teases the stallion
into arousal.
[Horse Neigh]
>> Once he gets aroused, we
start the process of mixing up
the materials and then we would
pour the materials into the
casting tube. And then we would
slide that tube over his
erection and hold it there for
5 minutes until it is set.
We back the teaser mare off. He
loses his erection, and then we
have our first negative cast.
[Music]
>> We make a mold out of that.
And then once that's done we can
pour our toys into that mold. We
have custom colors, we can
pretty much pour our toys into
almost any color that you can
think of. Currently, we
have life casts of humans,
dogs and horses.
We have casted a Great
Pyrenees, a St. Bernard and an
Australian Shepherd. I would
love to cast some smaller breeds
who appeal to more female
customers. They are a huge part
of this industry. We make
sculpted models that are based
off animal genitalia that we
cannot life cast because it's
just not a possibility.
We have an elephant trunk,
a giraffe tongue, deer, rhinos,
hippocampus, dinosaurs, orca
whales. Well, you probably could
cast an orca whale, but you know
getting the availability. No
matter what's out there, there
is someone who has had sexual
attraction to it. We 3-D print
all of these models. I have a
3-D artist that lives in the
Czech republic and he does
amazing work with turning ideas
into actual objects.
Our price ranges
anywhere from $35-$300.
The first year we sold about 500
units. This last year we sold
over 2000. Our largest model is
Jackson, which is 22 inches in
length and 3 1/2 inches in
girth. Uh, we have a few
negative reviews but, mostly we
find that the customer just
ordered a toy that is too large
for them and they kind of count
it as a negative because they
can't use it because it's too
large. It just takes years
usually to train your body to be
able to, you know, take such
large objects. You are actually
modifying your body in a way.
Your sigmoid colon, that's a
curve in your intestines, and
people who get really extreme
into this stuff will actually
straighten that out to make it
so that they are able to acquire
larger objects into them.
And then you have the people who
actually really get turned on by
the fact that they are
cast off actual horses.
>> A lot of people can be into
bestiality. They are physically
attracted to the animals.
People who just
like large objects,
certain physical features,
just connecting with an animal
that size. Being with them
and interacting with them.
I mean, you get
attached to an animal.
Our toys are a lot safer
for everyone involved.
It's a great outlet for
their customer instead of
partaking in bestiality. I have
been called an artist by quite a
few people even though I don't
quite feel like one.
I am just representing what
mother nature has already made.
>> Lust, a sin that has truly so
many faces. Really, why should
we suppress such indelible urges
that are so elemental. I mean,
after all, who is ultimately the
most satisfied in this world.
The ones who bite the apple or
the ones who just stare at it?
Until Next time. You're a
good dog, aren't you.
You're a good boy.
Uploaded by [ sRtFeVeR ] new srt source
[Music]